Strudler, Robert U.S. Home Corporation Records 6388
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Robert Strudler U.S. Home Corporation Records
1971-2000
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
U.S. Home Corporation
Strudler, Robert J.
6388
17 cubic feet
17 linear ft.
Records.
8547506
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 01, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 08, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
8547506
- Issue and Sale of 100,000 Shares of Class A Capital Stock, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Acquisition of All of the Outstanding Capital Stock of Dee Wood Industries, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Scope and Contents
  July 1
- Acquisition of Imperial Land Corporation (and Affiliated Company) and Issue and Sale of Bonds and Stock. (Vol. 1/3), 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Issued and sold: $4,000,000, 6% Convertible, Subordinated Debentures, Due 1984; and 315,000 Shares of Common Stock
- Acquisition of Imperial Land Corporation (and Affiliated Company) and Issue and Sale of Stock and Bonds (Vol. 2/3), 1969 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Issued and Sold: $4,000,000, 6%, convertible, subordinated debentures due 1984; 315,000 shares of common stock
- Acquisition of Imperial Land Corporation (and Affiliated Company) and Issue and Sale of Stock and Bonds (Vol. 3/3), 1969 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Original Listing of Common Stock ON American Stock Exchange, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Acquisition of All The Outstanding Capital Stock of Port Builders, Inc., 1971 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  January 29
- Acquisition of All the Outstanding Capital Stock of First Development Corporation of America, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  February 2
- Acquisition of All the Outstanding Capital Stock of Soble Construction Co., 1971 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Acquisition of All the Outstanding Capital Stock of Ellis Suggs Construction Corporation, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  February 3
- Underwritten Public Offering and Sale of 700,000 Shares of Common Stock; Public Offering and Sale of 16,665 Shares of Common Stock (Vol. 1/2), 1971 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Underwritten Offering March 2 at Par Value $.10/share; Public Offering March 31 at Par Value $.10/Share
- Underwritten Public Offering and Sale of 700,000 Shares of Common Stock; Public Offering and Sale of 16,665 Shares of Common Stock (Vol. 2/2), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Purchase of All The Outstanding Capital Stock of Orrin E. Thompson Construction Corp., 1971 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  March 10
- Acquisition of All the outstanding Capital Stock of East Construction Co., 1971 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  March 31
- Acquisition of All the Outstanding Capital Stock of East Construction Co., 1971 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  March 31. This is US Home & Development's copy; the proceeding version is their lawyer's. They're identical.
- Original Listing Application to the New York Stock Exchange, Inc., 1971 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  July 6
- Acquisition of All the Outstanding Capital Stock of Stuart S. Golding, Inc., 1971 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  October 1
- Purchase of All the Outstanding Capital Stock of Marved Construction and Investments, Inc., 1971 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  October 5
- Acquisition of Norwood Homes, Inc., 1971 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  November 24
- Acquisition of Witkin Homes, Inc. and its Affiliated Corporations, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  November 26
- Issue of Stock and Bonds (vol. 1/2), 1971 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  $20,000,000 5.5% convertible, subordinated debentures, and 729,662 shares of common stock (par value $.10 per share)
- Issue of Stock and Bonds (Vol. 2/2), 1971 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  $20,000,000 5.5% convertible subordinated debentures and 729,662 shares of common stock (par value $.10 per share)
- Issue of Stock and Bonds (Exhibits) (Vol. 1/2), 1971 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Issue of Stock and Bonds (Exhibits) (Vol. 2/2), 1971 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Acquisition of Jordan-Caldwell Inc., 1972 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  June 12
- Settlement Agreement with Former Stockholders of First Development Corp., and Sale of The Mountains by First Development Corporation to First Communities of America Corp., 1973 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  June 26
- Acquisition of PBC Industries Inc. and PBC Products Inc., 1972 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  July 27
- Acquisition of 3H Building Corporation in Exchange for 535,993 Shares of U.S. Home Corporation Common Stock, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  October 3
- $50,000,000 Principal Amount 10% Notes Due 1987 (Vol. 1/2), 1977 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  August 30
- $50,000,000 Principal Amount 10% Notes Due 1987, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Public Offering and Sale of 1,000,000 Shares of Common Stock, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  August 20
- Acquisition of Brigadier Industries Corporation, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  January 7
- Purchase of All the Outstanding Capital Stock of Interstate Homes, Inc., 1983 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  February 16
- Shelf Registration of $100,000,000 of Debt Securities, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  December 4
- 50,000 unites of $50,000,000 reset notes Due April 15, 2000 With 5,000,000 Common Stock Purchase Warrants (Vol. 1/2), 1985 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  April 12
- 50,000 units of $50,000,000 Reset Notes Due April 15, 2000 With 5,000,000 Common Stock Purchase Warrants (Vol. 2/2), 1985 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Registration of $100,000,000 Subordinated Debt Securities, 5,000,000 Common Stock Purchase Warrants, 5,000,000 Shares of Common Stock, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  June 21
- $100,000,000 12 3/8% Senior Subordinated Notes Due June 1, 1996, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  June 30
- $75,000,000 Debtor-In-Possession Financing with GE Capital Corp. (Vol. 1/3), 1991 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  May 8
- $75,000,000 Debtor-In-Possession Financing with GE Capital Corp. (Vol. 2/3), 1991 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- $75,000,000 Debtor-In-Possession Financing with GE Capital Corp. (Vol.3/3), 1991 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Chapter 11 Plan of Reorganization and Restructuring of $443,000,000 of Debt and Other Liabilities (Vol. 1/4), 1993 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Chapter 11 Plan of Reorganization and Restructuring of $443,000,000 of Debt and Other Liabilities (Vol. 2/4), 1993 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Chapter 11 Plan of Reorganization and Restructuring of $443,000,000 of Debt and Other Liabilities (Vol.3/4), 1993 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Chapter 11 Plan of Reorganization and Restructuring of $443,000,000 of Debt and Other Liabilities (Vol.4/4), 1993 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Public Offering of $200,000,000 Principal Amount 9.75% Senior Notes Due 2003 to Refinance Certain Plan of Reorganization of Debt (Vol. 1/2), 1993 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Public Offering of $200,000,000 Principal Amount 9.75% Senior Notes Due 2003 to Refinance Certain Plan of Reorganization of Debt (Vol. 2/2), 1993 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- $95,000,000 Post Reorganization Secured Revolving Working Capital Facility with GE Capital Corp (Vol. 1/3), 1993 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- $95,000,000 Post Reorganization Secured Revolving Working Capital Facility with GE Capital Corp (Vol. 2/3), 1993 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- $95,000,000 Post Reorganization Secured Revolving Working Capital Facility with GE Capital Corp (Vol. 3/3), 1993 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Public Offering of $80,000,000 Principal Amount 4 7/8% Convertible Subordinated Debentures Due 2005 (Vol. 1/3), 1993 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  November 3-23
- Public Offering of $80,000,000 Principal Amount 4 7/8% Convertible Subordinated Debentures Due 2005 (Vol. 2/3), 1993 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Public Offering of $80,000,000 Principal Amount 4 7/8% Convertible Subordinated Debentures Due 2005 (Vol. 3/3), 1993 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- $130,000,000 Credit Agreement with The First national Bank of Chicago, as Agent, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  September 29
- Public Offering of $75,000,000 Principal Amount 7.95% Senior Notes Due 2001 (Vol. 1/3), 1996 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Public Offering of $75,000,000 Principal Amount 7.95% Senior Notes Due 2001 (Vol. 2/3), 1996 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Public Offering of $75,000,000 Principal Amount 7.95% Senior Notes Due 2001 (Vol. 3/3), 1997 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  May 28
- Public Offering of Notes and Other Associated Refinancing Transactions (Vol. 1/3), 1997 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  August 28. $225,000,000 Principal Amount $100,000,000 8.25% Senior Notes Due 2004; $125,000,000 8.88% Senior Subordinated Notes due 2007
- Public Offering of Notes and Associated Refinancing Transactions (Vol. 2/3), 1997 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Offering of Notes and Associated Refinancing Transactions (Vol. 3/3), 1997 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Public Offering of $100,000,000 Principal Amount 7.75% Senior Notes Due 2005 (Vol. 1/2), 1998 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  January 21
- Public Offering of $100,000,000 Principal Amount 7.75% Senior Notes Due 2005 (Vol. 2/2), 1998 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Geg, Gig, and Ush Purchase Agreement and Gigdi and Ush Joint Venture (Vol. 1/2), 1998 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  April 30
- Geg, Gig, and Ush Purchase Agreement and Gigdi and Ush Joint Venture (Vol. 2/2), 1998 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- $300,000,000 Second Amended and Restated Credit Agreement with The First national bank of Chicago, as Agent, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  September 11
- Public Offering of $125,000,000 Principal Amount 8.875% Senior Subordinated Notes Due 2009 (vol. 1/2), 1999 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  February 19
- Public Offering of $125,000,000 Principal Amount 8.875% Senior Subordinated Notes Due 2009 (vol. 2/2), 1999 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Acquisition of Lundgren Bros. Construction, Inc., 1999 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  April 19
- Lennar Corporation: Acquisition of U.S. Home Corporation (Vol. 1/3), 2000 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  May 2-3
- Lennar Corporation: Acquisition of U.S. Home Corporation (Vol. 2/3), 2000 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Lennar Corporation: Acquisition of U.S. Home Corporation (Vol. 3/3), 2000 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Merger of U.S. Home Corp. with Len Acquisition Corporation, a Wholly-Owned Subsidiary of Lennar Corporation, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  May 2